<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    
	<atom:link href="https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Badge Connect Guide</title>
      <link>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/main/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/main/</guid>
      <description>Badge Connect Guide A developer resource for implementers of Open Badges 2.1 Badge Connect API, released as Open Badges 2.1 brings the concept of a Federated backpack to the Open Badges ecosystem. A backpack is a service that acts as an agent for a recipient of Open Badges.
You can view code examples of each section of the guide.
This guide is sponsored by the Badgr Team at Concentric Sky.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Badge Connect Applications</title>
      <link>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/relying-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/relying-party/</guid>
      <description>Badge Connect Applications This section of the guide will explain how to get started with a relying party application for Badge Connect. Both Issuer apps and Displayer apps need to go through several common processes before the workflows for their specific needs diverge. Here we will explain these steps, including:
 Backpack Selection Dynamic Client Registration The OAuth Dance: Authorization Code &amp;amp; Token Exchange Refreshing Tokens  Then the remaining sections of the guide will provide step-by-step instructions for accessing the API endpoints necessary to build Issuer and Displayer applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Issuer Applications</title>
      <link>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/issuer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/issuer/</guid>
      <description>Issuer Applications: What you Need to Know Here is a guide for how to build a prototypical issuer application that awards Open Badges and pushes them to a recipient&amp;rsquo;s backpack of choice.
Issuer Apps step by step  A user starts on an issuing application and earns a badge. For example, they successfully complete a quiz. An Open Badges Assertion is published, linked to a BadgeClass and Issuer Profile, according to the Open Badges 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Displayer Applications</title>
      <link>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/displayer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://concentricsky.github.io/badge-connect-guide/displayer/</guid>
      <description>Displayer Applications: What you Need to Know Here is a guide for how to build a prototypical displayer application that pulls badge awards from a recipient&amp;rsquo;s backpack of choice and does something interesting with them. This example use case will be to display badges on a timeline to the user.
Displayer Apps step by step  A user starts on an badge displayer application and sees they have the opportunity to use the app by connecting their backpack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>